ACTWU Legislative and Political Department Files 5619/033
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Hull Dye and Print Works, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Huntington Apparel MFG Corporation, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Tarra Hall Clothiers-- Murray Goldstein, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Illinois Glove Company, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- EDA Loan, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- TRADE: Ad Hoc Subsides code, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- TRADE- Coated Fabrics, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- TRADE- American Textile Manufacturers Institute Plan, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Trade Resolution- US Conference of Mayors, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Trade and Tariff Act of 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Domestic Content Legislation- Testimony, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Crafted with Pride, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- TRADE- China, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- TRADE- China Countervailing Duties, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Labor Law Reform, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Labor Law- Correspondence From Senators, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  October 11
- Labor Law Reform- House, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Labor Law - Senate, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Labor Law Reforms- Reports on House Members, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Labor Law Reform- Votes, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Labor Law- Testimony, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Reform, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Labor Law Reform, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Trade, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Trade: Apparel Imports, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Bus Tour, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Cope School Speaker`s Biography, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Cope Scholl- Quality Hotel on Capitol Hill Contract, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- COPE School Delegates- Registration and Checks, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- COPE School Groups, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- COPE School - Delegate Character, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- COPE- Schedule, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Confirmation Letters to House Members, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Edward Kennedy's Letter, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- COPE School Speaker, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- COPE- Completed Questionnaires, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- COPE Legislation Masters, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- COPE: Delegate Appointment Letters, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- COPE School - Letters, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- COPE School, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  copies of checks
- COPE List, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  pictures
- COPE- Quality Hotel Food and Beverage, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- COPE School Institution, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 1989 COPE School (Box 13, Folder 5)
- COPE School, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Senate Poll Races, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- ACTWU- Members, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Campaign"92" - ACTWU Trade Packet, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Congress, 1973-1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Campaign Letters, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Campaign: Letters to the Field, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- ACTWU Letters, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Department of Labor: Labor Advisory Commission for Trade Negotiations, 1976-1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- ACTWU Letters to Congress, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Department of Labor: Labor Advisory Commission for Trade Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Letters to Congress, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Sessions at the Governor`s House Holiday Inn, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Department of Labor: Labor Advisory Commission for Trade Negotiations, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- ACTWU COPE- Legislative Institute- Changes for Next Year, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Lobby Contact Sheet, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- ACTWU COPE- Legislative Institute Schedules, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- ACTWU COPE- Legislative Institute, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- 1987 ACTWU- COPE- Legislative Institute (Box 14, Folder 11)
- ACTWU, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- The Citizens Trade Resolution 246 Press Packet, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- ACTWU: NAFTA, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Congressional Action: NAFTA, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Congressional: Moving to Mexico, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Opponents of North American Free Trade Agreement, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- General Agreement on Trade and Tariffs (GATT), 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Textile and Apparel Bill Information, 1991-2002 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Textile and Apparel bill, 1992-2002 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- North American Free Trade Agreement, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Citizen Trade Watch Campaign, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  December
- Liz Trade Files: Citizen Trade Watch, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Repots and Studies: North America Free Trade Agreement, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Liz Smith- Expense Reports, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Liz Smith- Expense Reports, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Liz Smith- Expense Reports, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Liz Smith- Expense Reports, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Liz Smith - Expense Reports, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Liz Smith - Expense Reports, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Michael J Wilson - Expense Reports, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Michael J Wilson - Expense Reports, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Michael J Wilson - Expense Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Michael J Wilson - Expense Reports, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- ACTWU- Bills, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- ACTWU- Bills, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- ACTWU - Bills, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- ACTWU- Bills, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- ACTWU- Bills, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- ACTWU- Bills, 1984-1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- 1986 Elections (Box 16, Folder 4)
- 1993 Inaugural (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Labor Party, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ACTWU- Clinton and Gore Campaign (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Clinton and Gore Campaign, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Brochure
- Democratic National Convention: Delegates, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Democratic National Committee Meeting, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  July 17
- Democratic National Committee: Delegate Selection, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Democratic National Committee: Delegate Selection, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Democratic National Committee: Delegates, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Democratic National Committee; Senate Brochures, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Democratic National Convention: Delegates, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Democratic National Convention: Delegate Election, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- 1988 Campaign (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Liz Smith- Campaign letters, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Labor Unity Edition, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  October
- COPE Clip Sheet, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Register to Vote, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  Poster
- Presidential Brochure, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Senate Brochure, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- 1988 Presidential Candidate (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Presidential Questionnaires, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Democratic National Convention: Registration Drive Brochure, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Democratic National Convention: Delegate, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Vetoes of Bush, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Jerry Brown, 1975-1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Tom Harkin, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Bob Kerrey, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Paul Tsongas, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  A Call to Economic Arms
- Patrick J Buchanan, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Ross Perot, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Democratic National Convention, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- The Poll report, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- 1984 Election Vote Analysis (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Voting Report, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- National Right to Work Committee Complaint, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Mondale- Ferraro Brochure, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Federal Election Commission, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Democratic National Convention: Delegates, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Democratic National Convention-Delegates, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Federal Election Commission- Communication with Members, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- ACTWU- Mailings, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Missouri Federal Election Commission Reports, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Pennsylvania Federal Election Commission Report, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Federal Election Commission Complaint- Sasser, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Presidential Campaign delegates, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Mondale Campaign, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Political: Labor for Carter/Mondale, 1980-1987 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- The Gephardt Amendment, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- S680, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  April 10
- Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Veto Message of Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Grassroots Campaign, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Congressional record, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Trade Enforcement Act of 1985- Lobby letters (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Trade Enforcement Act of 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Letters
- Direct Mail Campaign, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Baker Report Fact Sheet, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Trade Enforcement Act of 1985- Thank you letters (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Trade Enforcement Act of 1985- Letters to Congress (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Trade Enforcement Act of 1985- Letters to Congress, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- General Agreement on Trade and Tariffs, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Letters to President on Multi- Fiber Agreement, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- American textile Manufacturers Institute Letter in Support of Mandatory Reporting of Textile and Apparel Products, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  April 29
- Multifiber Agreement- Letter to President from House, 1985-1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- 1986 Campaign Letters to State and International Presidents, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Jobs, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Losing Our Shirts brochures, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Jobs, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  posters
- ACTWU News, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Names and Addresses of those who receive Leadership News, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- 1986 Campaign- Mailing Information (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Radio Commercial for Veto Override, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Statements by House on behalf of our Bill, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  July 15
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act (Box 18, Folder 31)
  Transcript: Leonard Mobley
- Congressional Record, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Mailings to Field in Bill, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Textile and Trade Enforcement Act- 99th Congress: ACTWU Testimony, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Testimony to Trade Subcommittee in House, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Mr. Textile Brochures and Photos, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Senate Banking Committee Testimony, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  June
- Testimony: Nida and Elli, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Statements: Senate Finance Committee, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Statements: Trade Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Statements: Trade Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Mailings to Field on Bill, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Mailings, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Action Pact for Veto Override, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Rally to Override Veto, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  July 30
- ACTWU Bills, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- FFACT Fact Sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- History of Unfair Trade Cases, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- ACTWU Fact Sheets, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- MFA: John Gregg`s Speech, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Textile and Import Crisis, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Gloversville Case, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- CUT-OUTS: Dennis Gill and Nola Jennings, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Targets, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Fact Sheets: Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Congressional Record- Senate, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Congressional Record- Senate, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Congressional Record Remarks, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Fibers, textiles, and imports, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- US Imports, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Research, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Textile Trade Information, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Employment, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Textiles and Jobs, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Earnings of textile workers in different countries, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Economic Forecast Fact Sheet, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Employment Losses in Textiles, 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Employment in Textile Industries, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Sample Letter to Representative, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- FFACT Press Clips, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Textile Bill Fact Sheet, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Multi-Fiber Arrangement Bill, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Background Material, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- FFACT Sheets, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act Ads, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- FFACT: Deindustrialization Report, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Co-Sponsors, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO. 1980 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO. 1979 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- AFL-CIO. 1978 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- AFL-CIO. 1977 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- AFL-CIO. 1976 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO. 1975 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO. 1974 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO. 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- AFL-CIO. 1972 (Box 20, Folder 29)
- AFL-CIO. 1970 (Box 20, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO. 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- AFL-CIO. 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- AFL-CIO. 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- AFL-CIO. 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- AFL-CIO. 1959-1960 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- AFL-CIO. 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 36)
- AFL-CIO. 1947-1956 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- 1986 Campaign (Box 20, Folder 38)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Statement on The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Response Letters to Multi- Fiber Arrangement, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- FFACT Sheet: Battle Plan, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Opposition Congressional Black Caucus, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Consumer Information, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Ambassador Yeutter, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 45)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Opposition Letter from Thomas McAn Worker, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Consumer Mailings, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Members of Congress who Switched on Us, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 48)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Lobbyist Against, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Opposition, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 50)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Opposition, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Opposition, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Textile Import Legislation, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Betrayal by Boors, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Override of 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Veto Override, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Opposition, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- FFACT Sheets, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Veto Override Supporters, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- H.R. 1562 Rally, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Lobbying, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Lobbying, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: May Department Store, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: facts sheet, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Veto Override, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Textile Bill: Senators not supporting it, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Members of Congress Visited by ACTWU Delegates, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Thank You, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Retail Coalition, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- TRADE: World Wide Quotas, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Trade: Thailand, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- US- China Trade, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- TRADE- South Korea, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Labeling Act, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- TRADE- Taiwan, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- TRADE- Taiwan, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Textile Bill, 1987-1991 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Consumers, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Textile Recovery Act, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Labor Institutes, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Finley`s Testimony on The Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- PACs and lobbies, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Washington Post on Trade, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  July 5
- Negotiations on Free Trade Area Agreements, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Democratic National Convention 1986 Override (Box 22, Folder 4)
- US Import of Neckties, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- US Import of Neckties, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Articles on Bill(H.R 1562) Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- TRADE- Multi- Fiber Agreement, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Import Restrictions Poll, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  article- June 9
- Textile and Apparel Trade Bill: Opposition Importers Propaganda and Disinformation, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  Statement of September 18
- Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act: Supporting Letters, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Asia- Pacific Council of American Chambers of Commerce, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Foreign Imports- Brazil, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  August 5
- Foreign Imports- Caribbean Basin, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Foreign Imports- Japan, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  September 12
- Hong Kong- Taiwan Agreement, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Textile Caucus Letters, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Fiber, Fabric, and Apparel Coalition for Trade, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Cotton Exports, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Chronological Correspondence, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Chronological Correspondence, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Chronological Correspondence, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Chronological Correspondence, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Chronological Correspondence, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Chronological Correspondence, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Chronological Correspondence, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  February 15-17
- Democratic Senate Campaign Committee, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- 101st Congress- ACTWU Mailings to Hill, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Trade in Textiles and Apparel, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Contributors of ACTWU
- ACTWU- Mailing to Field, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage; 101st Congress, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Economic Perspectives Incorporate Report, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- 100th Congress, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Liz Smith`s Traveling Record, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Israel- general, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Trip to Israel, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  January 5-14
- Women`s Conference in Argentina, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  November
- Trip to Argentina, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- ACTWU- ILGWU Zensen Meeting, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Trade with China, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- FFACT, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - FFACT Updates, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  clippings
- 101st Congress- Proposal for New Textile Legislation, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - OTA Report, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Vote on Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - Senate Cosponsors, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - House Cosponsors, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Directory- United States Senate, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Directory- United States House of Representatives, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Senate Votes on Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Partisan Voting Breakdown on Trade Bill, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Map of Capitol Hill, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - Talking Points, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Textiles, Apparel, and Footwear- Essential to Defense, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - Footwear Industry, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - Summary, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - White Paper, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - Questions and Answers, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Legislative Approach to trade, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Proposed textile legislation for US agriculture, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Agricultural versus Textile Imports, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- EPI Study on Agriculture, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - FFACT Sheet, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- FACT Sheet- GATT Compatibility, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Testimony- Motes, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act - GATT issues, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- ICF Report- New Jobs, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Apparel Profits (Box 24, Folder 29)
- FFACT Sheet- Apparel Company Profits in 1986 Recovery, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- FFACT Sheet- Commerce Department Revises Textile Profits Down, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Poll- Textile Bill, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Textile Profits Issue- Fact Sheet Executive Summary, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Assorted Fact Sheets (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Statement/Speech Textile Bill, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- America`s Standard of Living Deteriorating, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 36)
- OTA Report- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Textile Trade- Quotas, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- ICF Report on Employees and Prices, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- OTA (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- - IBERC Study (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Textile Bill- Retaliation Caucus, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Bill Text (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Protectionism (Box 24, Folder 44)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Import Penetration (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Tariff Cuts/ Compensation Issues (Box 24, Folder 46)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Exchange Rate Issues (Box 24, Folder 47)
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Capacity Utilization Issues (Box 24, Folder 48)
- Imports Balloon- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  June 12
- Textile Bill Fact Sheets, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- FFACT Drafts, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- JCF Report- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- Transfer Payment (Box 24, Folder 52)
- Washington Post- World Leaders, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  July 26
- Textile and Apparel Trade Act of 1987- (Box 24, Folder 54)
  Statistics
- Textile Bill Fact Sheet- Military Need, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- ICF Report- Government Saves in Unemployment Progress, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- Women and Minorities in Textile/Apparel Industry, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- Textile and Apparel Imports from Iran, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- FFACT- Iran Imports, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 59)
- Child Labor- Washington Post, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  July 12
- Assorted letters to colleagues, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- Wages in Textile Industry, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 62)